Labor Arbitration Opinions and Awards 5443
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Labor Arbitration Opinions and Awards
1955-1993
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
University of California at Los Angeles
5443
39.5 cubic feet
39.5 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Miscellaneous arbitration papers collected over the years by the University of California, Los Angeles, and donated to the Industrial Labor Relations School in 1970. An index is located in box 40.
5649168
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, December 03, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 13, 2019
Scope and Contents
The folders are labeled Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards instead of Awards. Please note that the proper label should be Labor Arbitration Opinions and Awards and not Rewards.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Labor -- United States; University of California, Los Angeles
5649168
- Vols. 1-3: A - American Airmotive (Box 1)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards, 1958-1962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    December 1958 - December 1962
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards, 1959-1963 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    June 1959 - June 1963
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 1, 1958-1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Table of Contents
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 1, 1958-1964 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 1, 1959-1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 1, 1959-1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 1, 1958-1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 2, 1959-1962 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 2, 1957-1961 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 2, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 2, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 2, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 2, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 2, 1957-1964 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 2, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 3, 1960-1964 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 3, 1957-1963 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 3, 1958-1963 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 3, 1957-1963 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Vols. 3-5: American Art - American Radiator (Box 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 3, 1959-1963 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 3, 1958-1963 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 3, 1959-1964 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 3, 1959-1964 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 4, 1957-1964 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 4, 1958-1963 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 4, 1957-1963 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 4, 1958-1964 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 5, 1959-1964 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 5, 1958-1963 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 5, 1958-1961 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 5, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 5, 1958-1963 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 5, 1959-1963 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Vols. 6-8: American Roller - Armstrong Cork (Box 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 6, 1957-1964 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 6, 1960-1963 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 6, 1961-1964 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 6, 1959-1964 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 6, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 6, 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 6, 1957-1964 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 7, 1957-1963 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 7, 1961-1963 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 7, 1957-1964 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 7, 1959-1963 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 7, 1958-1964 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 7, 1953-1963 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 7, 1958-1961 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 7, 1961-1963 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 7, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 8, 1958-1963 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 8, 1959-1964 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Vols. 8-10: Armstrong Cork - Belock Instrument (Box 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 8, 1957-1963 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 8, 1959-1964 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 8, 1958-1963 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 8, 1958-1963 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 8, 1959-1963 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 9, 1959-1963 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 9, 1957-1963 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 9, 1957-1963 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 9, 1957-1963 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 9, 1957-1963 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 9, 1957-1964 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 9, 1957-1961 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 9, 1960-1964 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 10, 1960-1963 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 10, 1958-1963 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 10, 1957-1963 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 10, 1959-1963 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Beloit Iron Works to Bethlehem Steel (Box 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.10, 1957-1963 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.10, 1960-1964 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.10, 1957-1962 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.11, 1956-1964 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.11, 1956-1958 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.11, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.11, 1957-1958 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.11, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.11, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.11, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.12, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.12, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.12, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.12, 1958-1961 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.12, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.12, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.12, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.12, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.12, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Vols. 13-14: Beth - Brun (Box 6)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.13, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Table of Contents. Bethlehem Steel Co. to Bolen's Division
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.13, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.13, 1958-1964 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.13, 1958-1964 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.13, 1958-1963 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.13, 1959-1964 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.13, 1961-1964 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.14, 1959-1963 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    Table of Contents. Bonafide Mills Co. to Bruning (Charles) Co., Inc.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.14, 1959-1963 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.14, 1957-1961 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.14, 1961-1962 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.14, 1957-1963 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.14, 1959-1963 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Vols. 15-16: Brun - Celanese (Box 7)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.15, 1961-1963 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Table of Contents. Bruning (Charles) Co., Inc. to Capital Airlines Pilots' Merger Committee
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.15, 1958-1964 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.15, 1958-1963 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.15, 1959-1964 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.15, 1958-1964 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.15, 1957-1964 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.15, 1958-1964 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.16, 1957-1963 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    Table of Contents. Capital City Corp. to Celanese Fiber Co.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.16, 1957-1963 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.16, 1958-1964 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.16, 1961-1962 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.16, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.16, 1959-1962 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.16, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    One document from 1962 included
- Vols. 17-18: Celanese - Chrysler (Box 8)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.17, 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Table of Contents. Celanese Fiber Co. to Charleston Clay Products Co.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.17, 1963-1964 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.17, 1961-1964 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.17, 1962-1963 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.17, 1957-1964 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.17, 1961-1964 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.17, 1960-1964 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.17, 1957-1964 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.17, 1958-1963 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.18, 1958-1963 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Table of Contents. Charleston Transit Co. to Chrysler Corp.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.18, 1957-1964 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.18, 1958-1964 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.18, 1957-1963 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.18, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.18, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Vols. 19-20: Chrysler - Clou (Box 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 19, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Table of Contents. Chrysler Corporation
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 19, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 19, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 19, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 19, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 19, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 20, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Table of Contents. Chrysler Corporation to Claugherty Packing Co.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 20, 1956-1964 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 20, 1958-1964 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 20, 1957-1963 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 20, 1957-1963 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 20, 1958-1964 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Vols. 21-22: Clov - Continental Oil (Box 10)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 21, 1957-1963 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Table of Contents. Cloverland Diary Products to Combustion Engineering Inc.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 21, 1957-1963 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 21, 1957-1962 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 21, 1961-1964 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 21, 1957-1964 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 21, 1959-1963 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 21, 1959-1963 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 22, 1957-1964 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    Table of Contents. Commercial Solvent Corp. to Continental Oil Co.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 22, 1957-1964 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 22, 1959-1964 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 22, 1957-1963 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 22, 1961-1963 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Vols. 23-24: Continental Pacific - Dave (Box 11)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 23, 1959-1963 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Table of Contents. Continental Pacific Lines to Crane Company
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 23, 1957-1963 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.23, 1957-1963 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.23, 1957-1964 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.23, 1957-1963 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.24, 1958-1963 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Table of Contents. Crandton Print Works Co. to Devaga Stores Corp.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.24, 1957-1964 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.24, 1959-1962 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.24, 1958-1963 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.24, 1957-1963 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Vols. 25-26: Davi - Dough (Box 12)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.25, 1958-1963 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Table of Contents. Davidson Enamel Products Co. to Deere And Co.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.25, 1957-1963 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.25, 1957-1959 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.25, 1961-1963 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.25, 1957-1964 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.25, 1957-1961 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.26, 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    Table of Contents. Deere And Co. to Doughboy Plastics Production, Inc.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.26, 1957-1964 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.26, 1958-1963 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.26, 1957-1964 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.26, 1959-1964 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.26, 1957-1963 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Vols. 27-28: Dougl - Erw (Box 13)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 27, 1959-1964 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Table of Contents. Douglass Aircraft Co, Inc. to Eldon Industries Inc.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 27, 1957-1964 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 27, 1957-1963 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 27, 1957-1962 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 27, 1958-1964 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 27, 1958-1963 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 28, 1957-1963 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    Table of Contents. Electric Auto-Line to Erin Mills Co.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 28, 1957-1961 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 28, 1958-1964 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 28, 1958-1964 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 28, 1957-1963 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 28, 1957-1961 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Vols. 29-30: Erw - Fre (Box 14)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 29, 1958-1963 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    Table of Contents. Erwin Mills, Inc., to Fire Paper Division
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 29, 1960-1963 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 29, 1957-1963 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 29, 1958-1963 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 29, 1958-1964 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 29, 1957-1963 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 30, 1958-1963 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    Table of contents. Firch Baking Co. to Freightliner Corp.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 30, 1957-1964 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 30, 1958-1963 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 30, 1957-1964 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 30, 1957-1963 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 30, 1957-1963 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Vols. 31-32: Fre - General (Box 15)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 31, 1958-1963 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Table of Contents. Freightliner Corp. to Greenlan-Kilmartin Co.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 31, 1957-1963 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 31, 1961-1963 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 31, 1958-1964 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 31, 1957-1963 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 31, 1957-1963 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 32, 1958-1963 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    Table of Contents. Gehl Guernsey Farms, Inc. to General Tire AND Rubber Co.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 32, 1958-1963 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 32, 1958-1962 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 32, 1960-1962 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 32, 1958-1964 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 32, 1958-1963 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Vols. 33-34: General - Gulf States P (Box 16)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 33, 1958-1964 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Table of Contents. General Tire AND Rubber Co. to Grant Lunch Coro.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 33, 1957-1964 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 33, 1955-1964 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 33, 1957-1993 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 33, 1955-1964 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 33, 1959-1964 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 34, 1957-1963 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    Table of Contents. Grabibate Meat and Livestock Co. to Gulf States Paper Corp.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 34, 1957-1963 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 34, 1958-1964 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 34, 1957-1962 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 34, 1957-1964 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Vols. 35-36: Gulf States U - Holi (Box 17)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 35, 1954-1964 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    Table of Contents. Gulf States Utilities Co. to Heckett Engineering Co.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 35, 1957-1964 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 35, 1957-1963 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 35, 1952-1963 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 35, 1957-1964 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 35, 1959-1964 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 36, 1957-1963 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    Table of Contents. Heckett Engineering Co. to Hollister Coil Spring Co.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 36, 1957-1963 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 36, 1957-1963 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 36, 1957-1964 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 36, 1958-1963 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 36, 1959-1962 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Vols. 37-38: Holl - International Pipe (Box 18)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 37, 1957-1964 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Table of Contents. Hollinger Consolidated Gold Mines, LTD. To Illinois Bell Telephone Co.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 37, 1957-1963 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 37, 1957-1964 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 37, 1955-1964 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 37, 1957-1964 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 37, 1959-1963 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 38, 1957-1963 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    Table of Contents. Illinois Brick Co. to International Pipe and Ceramics Corp.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 38, 1958-1964 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 38, 1959-1963 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 38, 1958-1964 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 38, 1957-1963 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 38, 1958-1964 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Vols. 39-40: International Salt - Kim (Box 19)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 39, 1957-1964 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Table of Contents. International Salt Co. to KPT MGF. Co.